DOAN HUU NOI

+65-8434-2003 ♦ doanhuunoi@gmail.com ♦ noidh.github.io

EDUCATION

Soongsil University, Seoul, South Korea

Sept 2013 - July 2015

Master's Degree in Video & Image Processing.

Post and Telecom. Institute of Tech., HCM City, Vietnam

Sept 2008 - Jan 2013

Bachelor's Degree in Information Technology.

PUBLICATION

Google Scholar Profile

- 1. A Method for matching pattern using image and an apparatus of thereof, HN. Doan, KS. Kwon, S. Korea Domestic Patent, 2021, No:1024319840000, View Demo.
- 2. Method for hole filling in 3D model, and recording medium and apparatus for performing the same, US Patent, MC. Hong, BS. Kim, TD. Nguyen, HN. Doan, 2018, PDF.
- 3. Hole-Filling algorithm with spatio-temporal background information for view synthesis, IEICE Trans. on Information and Systems, HN. Doan, TD. Nguyen, MC. Hong, 2017, PDF.
- 4. A spatial-temporal hole filling approach with background modeling and texture synthesis for 3D video, Proceedings of the 2015 Conf. on research in adaptive and convergent systems, HN. Doan, MC. Hong, 2015, Link.
- 5. Hole filling algorithm using spatial-temporal background depth map for view synthesis in free view point television, Pacific Rim Conf. on Multimedia, HN. Doan, BS. Kim, MC. Hong, 2015, Link.
- 6. Directional hole filling algorithm in new view synthesis for 3D video using local segmentation, Proceedings of the 2014 Conf. on Research in Adaptive and Convergent Systems, HN. Doan, TA. Nguyen, MC. Hong, 2014, Link.

BACKGROUND

C++, Python, Pytorch, SIMD (SSE, AVX, NEON), TensorRT, OpenCV, Open3D, **Programming**

OpenGL, QT, MFC, CUDA, CMake

Research Image Processing, Computer Vision, Deep Learning, Stereo Vision, Depth Es-

timation, 3D Gaussian Splatting, Pattern Matching, Object Detection, Machine

Learning, 3D Rendering, Defect Inspection, Model Deployment

Language Vietnamese, Korean, English

EXPERIENCE

Zoom Nov. 2022 - Current Singapore

Video Processing Software Engineer

- · Participating in optimization tasks of the core image processing library.
- Participating in development of 3D-telepresence project:
- System setup: camera setup, intrinsic calibration, stereo calibration, multiple cameras synchroniza-
- Data collection: synthesis data, real data.
- Model training: Depth net (based on RAFT-Stereo), Render Net (based on 3DGS), optimizing using TensorRT.
- Design and implement the demo program: Using python, OpenGL Cubemap.

<u>Tech Stack:</u> C++, Python, Pytorch, SIMD, TensorRT, Open3D, OpenCV, OpenGL, Video Processing, Deep Learning, 3D Rendering, 3D Gaussian Splatting, Depth Estimation, Model Deployment.

MVTech Nov. 2018 - Nov.2022

Image Processing Researcher

South Korea

- · Participated in developing RAVID framework
 - Developed the Shape Finder algorithm which is a feature-based matching algorithm. (View Demo)
 - Developing very fast convolution and morphology operations by using SIMD and In-place Processing.
 - Developed an OCR algorithm based on NCC matching algorithm.
- · Developed defect inspection algorithms for automatic inspection machines.
- · <u>Tech Stack:</u> C++, SIMD, Image Processing, Computer Vision.

Enscape Feb. 2017 - Oct. 2018

Software Engineer South Korea

- · Developed defect inspection algorithms by using Halcon library.
- · Developed applications for Matrix machine, Auto-Handler machine.
- · <u>Tech Stack:</u> C++, MFC, Halcon, OpenCV, SIMD.

Chowis Sept 2015 - Oct. 2016

Software Engineer South Korea

- · Developed a Android application for a skin inspection kit.
- · Tech Stack: C++, Java, Android

PERSONAL PROJECTS

Technical Blog

I write articles to describe what I have learnt about Image Processing, Computer Vision, Machine Learning, 3D Rendering and other miscellaneous. Moreover, I develop the XImageTool application to demonstrate how those algorithms work intuitively.

XImageTool

XImageTool is a free tool used for simulating fundamental Image Processing, Computer Vision, Machine Learning algorithms and 3D Rendering.

XText

XText is a free OCR software.